Contact

781917299 (Home) yesiha2001@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ayesiza-hawah-339700185 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

React.js React Native Node.js

Certifications

Responsive Web Design
JavaScript Algorithms and Data
Structures

AYESIZA HAWAH

Software Developer

Uganda

Summary

Software Engineer, with three years of experience in website and software development. I'm technically proficient, easy to work with and I don't stop till it's perfect, so send me a quick email on yesiha2001@gmail.com to find out more about what I can do for you. Specialties: HTML5, CSS,Javascript, NodeJS, Reactjs

Experience

Outbox Uganda Software Engineer October 2020 - Present (1 year 6 months) Kampala, Uganda

- . Build the front-end of applications through appealing visual design.
- . Develop and manage well-functioning databases and applications.
- . Write effective APIs and Test built projects to ensure responsiveness and efficiency.
- . Mentor newbies in software Development

Airdady LLC Full Stack Developer June 2021 - Present (10 months) Uganda

- . Ensuring technical feasibility of UI/UX designs.
- . Maintaining and upgrading existing systems.
- . Writing and implementing reusable code for future use.

Andela Junior Software Engineer May 2019 - October 2020 (1 year 6 months)

Page 1 of 2

Kigali City, Rwanda

- . Worked as a Junior Developer at Andela kigali On Company projects like Free Mentors and Property Prolite projects.
- . Ensure learning of the codebase, attend design meetings, write basic code, and fix bugs.
- . Provide valuable support to the design team while continually improving their coding and design skills.
- . Ensuring the ability to learn new technologies quickly, and have the ability to work in a team environment.
- . Worked closely with designers to take wireframes from conception to implementation and design and improve user interfaces .

Education

Outbox uganda

software development, Software Technology/Development · (July 2020 - August 2021)

Islamic University in Uganda

Bachelor of Computer Science, Computer Software Engineering · (September 2012 - October 2015)

freeCodeCamp

Certification, Responsive Web Design and Javascript · (January 2021)